thedeal.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Welcome to The Deal

PRIVACY POLICIES 

LAST UPDATED: August 03, 2018

* * *

TheStreet, Inc. and its affiliates, including The Deal, LLC, BoardEx, LLC and Management Diagnostics Limited, (“ **TST** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”) are concerned about privacy issues and want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information that we collect through our websites currently located at TheDeal.com, BoardEx.com and any other website operated by us from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (the “ **Websites** ”), through the software applications made available by us for use on or through computers and mobile devices in connection with which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (the “ **Apps** ”), and through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, including the Websites and the Apps, the “ **Services** ”). By providing Personal Information to us or using the Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Personal Information We May Collect

“ **Personal Information** ” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person, including, for example:

  * Name
  * Job title and company
  * Address
  * Phone number
  * Email address
  * Social media account ID

### How We May Collect Personal Information

We and our service providers may collect Personal Information in a variety of ways, including:

  *  **Through the Services** : We may collect Personal Information through the Services, such as when you sign up for a newsletter.
  *  **Offline** : We may collect Personal Information from you offline, such as when you attend one of our live events, place an order over the phone or contact customer service.
  *  **From Other Sources** : We may receive your Personal Information from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, social media platforms (including from people with whom you are friends or otherwise connected) and from other third parties. For example, if you elect to connect your social media account to your Services account, certain Personal Information from your social media account will be shared with us, which may include Personal Information that is part of your profile or your friends’ profiles.

### How We May Use Personal Information

We and our service providers may use Personal Information:

  * To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you newsletters or to facilitate your participation in a webinar or other event.
  * To send administrative information to you, such as information regarding the Services and changes to our terms, conditions and policies.
  * To complete and fulfill your purchase, including to process your payment, have your order delivered to you, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related customer service.
  * To send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you, subject to any choices you have expressed with respect to such communications.
  * To personalize your experience on the Services by presenting products and offers tailored to you.
  * To request your participation in surveys and to administer such surveys.
  * To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information. We suggest that you read any such rules carefully.
  * To facilitate social sharing functionality.
  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities.

### How Personal Information May Be Disclosed

Your Personal Information may be disclosed:

  * To our affiliates, TheStreet, Inc., BoardEx LLC and Management Diagnostics Limited, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. The Deal LLC is the party responsible for the management of the jointly-used Personal Information.
  * To our third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing and other services.
  * To third parties, to permit them to send you marketing communications, subject to any choices you have expressed.
  * To a third-party provider of a product or service that you purchase through the Services.
  * To third-party sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions.
  * To identify you to anyone to whom you send messages through the Services.
  * By you, on message boards, chat, profile pages and blogs and other services to which you are able to post information and materials. Please note that any information you post or disclose through these services may be available to other users and the general public. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose any information on the Services.
  * To your friends associated with your social media account, to other users of the Services and to your social media account provider, in connection with your social sharing activity, such as if you connect your social media account to your Services account or log into your Services account from your social media account. By connecting your Services account and your social media account, you authorize us to share information with your social media account provider, and you understand that the use of the information we share will be governed by the social media site’s privacy policy.
  * To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

### Other Uses and Disclosures

We also may use and disclose your Personal Information as we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, which may include laws outside your country of residence; (b) to respond to requests from courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, and other public and government authorities, which may include such authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; and (e) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others.

## OTHER INFORMATION

### Other Information We May Collect

“ **Other Information** ” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individual, such as:

  * Browser and device information
  * App usage data
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies
  * Demographic and other information provided by you
  * Aggregated information

If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it for the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information as detailed in this Privacy Policy.

### How We May Collect Other Information

We and our third party service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including:

  *  **Through your browser or device** : Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language and Internet browser type and version. We use this information to ensure that the Services function properly.
  *  **Through your use of the App** : When you download and use the App, we may track and collect App usage data, such as the date and time the App on your device accesses our servers, the pages you use and what information and files have been downloaded to the App based on your device number.
  *  **Using cookies** : Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on your computer. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Services, pages visited, language preferences, and other anonymous traffic data. We and our service providers use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, to personalize your experience while using the Services and to recognize your computer in order to assist your use of the Services. We also gather statistical information about use of the Services in order to continually improve their design and functionality, understand how they are used and assist us with resolving questions about them. Cookies further allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on certain of the Services. We may also use cookies or other technologies to track responses to our online advertisements. At this time, we do not respond to browser do-not-track signals.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies or be given choices on how to manage them. You may also wish to refer to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html>. If, however, you do not accept cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Services. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer, and you may need to log in every time you visit.

  *  **Using pixel tags and similar technologies** : Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Services to, among other things, track the actions of users (including email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about use of the Services and response rates.
  *  **Analytics** : We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Services and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.
  *  **IP Address** : Your IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider. An IP address may be logged automatically in our server log files whenever you access the Services, along with the time of the visit and the pages visited. Collecting IP addresses is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels, diagnosing server problems and administering the Services. We may also derive your approximate location from your IP address.
  *  **From you** : We collect information such as your industry, geographic and deal focuses when you voluntarily provide it.
  *  **By aggregating information** : Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you (for example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code).

### How We May Use and Disclose Other Information

We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we combine Other Information with Personal Information, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined.

## THIRD PARTY SERVICES

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which the Services link. The inclusion of a link on the Services does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or by our affiliates. In addition, we are not responsible for the information collection, use, disclosure or security policies or practices of other organizations, such as Facebook, Apple, Google, Microsoft, RIM or any other app developer; app, social media platform, operating system or wireless service provider; or device manufacturer, including with respect to any Personal Information you disclose to other organizations through or in connection with the Apps.

## SECURITY

We use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures designed to protect Personal Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please also be aware that we may use third-party cloud service providers that provide hosting, data storage and other services pursuant to standard terms and conditions that may be non-negotiable; these service providers have informed us or the general public that they apply security measures they consider adequate for the protection of information within their systems, or they have a general reputation for applying such measures. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us in accordance with the “Contacting Us” section below.

## CHOICES AND ACCESS

### Your choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information

We give you choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information for marketing purposes. You may opt-out from:

  *  **Receiving electronic communications from us** : If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out by following the instructions contained in each such email or contacting us at [customerservice@thedeal.com](mailto:customerservice@thedeal.com) or [HelpDesk@BoardEx.com](mailto:HelpDesk@BoardEx.com).
  *  **Our sharing of your Personal Information with affiliates for their direct marketing purposes** : If you would prefer that we not share your Personal Information on a going-forward basis with our affiliates for their direct marketing purposes, you may opt-out of this sharing by writing to us at [customerservice@thedeal.com](mailto:customerservice@thedeal.com) or [HelpDesk@BoardEx.com](mailto:HelpDesk@BoardEx.com).
  *  **Our sharing of your Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes** : If you would prefer that we not share your Personal Information on a going-forward basis with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes, you may opt-out of this sharing by writing to us at [customerservice@thedeal.com](mailto:customerservice@thedeal.com) or [HelpDesk@BoardEx.com](mailto:HelpDesk@BoardEx.com).

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that if you opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send you important administrative messages, from which you cannot opt-out.

### How you can access, change or suppress your Personal Information

If you would like to review and change or update the name, email address and/or password associated with your account, you may do so by: for The Deal properties, calling us at 1-888-667-3325 or writing to us at customerservice@thedeal.com; and for BoardEx properties, by logging into your account. If you would like to suppress or delete Personal Information that you have previously provided to us, you may do so by contacting us at [customerservice@thedeal.com](mailto:customerservice@thedeal.com) or [HelpDesk@BoardEx.com](mailto:HelpDesk@BoardEx.com).

In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal Information suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of your Personal Information. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion.

## RETENTION PERIOD

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

## USE OF SERVICES BY MINORS

The Services are not directed to individuals under the age of eighteen (18). We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from such individuals, and we request that they not provide Personal Information through the Services.

## CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and, by using the Services, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country. In certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in those other countries may be entitled to access your Personal Information.

## SENSITIVE INFORMATION

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., Social Security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Services or otherwise to us.

## UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy. The “ _LAST UPDATED_ ” legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Your use of the Services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.

## CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [customerservice@thedeal.com](mailto:customerservice@thedeal.com) or:

  * Customer Service
  * The Deal
  * 14 Wall Street
  * New York, NY 10005

Because email communications are not always secure, please do not include credit card or other sensitive information in your emails to us.

Sophisticated insight to **generate deal flow, improve client intelligence** and **enhance market knowledge.**[REQUEST A DEMO](http://thedeal.com/request-a-demo)
